<resources>
    <string name="app_name">eshop</string>

    <string name="login_preference">advhci.ihu.gr.loginappsharedpreferences_loginPreference</string>
    <string name="login_status">advhci.ihu.gr.loginappsharedpreferences_loginStatus</string>
    <string name="user_name">margaret</string>
    <string name="user_password">blue</string>
    <string name="user_name2">alkis</string>
    <string name="user_password2">miro</string>
    <string name="about">
        Welcome to our e-shop, your one-stop destination for all your online shopping needs! Our online store offers a wide range of products from various categories, including electronics, fashion, home and garden, beauty and personal care, sports and outdoors, and many more.
        We strive to provide our customers with the best possible shopping experience by offering a user-friendly website that is easy to navigate. Our product pages are filled with detailed descriptions, high-quality images, and customer reviews to help you make informed purchasing decisions.
        We also offer competitive pricing and regular discounts and promotions to ensure that you get the best value for your money. Our checkout process is quick and secure, and we accept multiple payment methods, including credit cards, PayPal, and other online payment services.
        At our e-shop, we prioritize customer satisfaction, and our friendly and knowledgeable customer service team is always available to assist you with any questions or concerns you may have. We also offer hassle-free returns and exchanges to ensure that you are completely satisfied with your purchase.
        Thank you for choosing our e-shop for your online shopping needs. Happy shopping!
    </string>



    <string-array name="all_strings_username">
        <item>@string/user_name</item>
        <item>@string/user_name2</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="all_strings_passwords">
        <item>@string/user_password</item>
        <item>@string/user_password2</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>